{
    "subject": "resource/Edward_Felten",
    "predicate": "ontology/citizenship",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "Edward Felten is a citizen of United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9875263571739197,
            "question": "Is Edward Felten a citizen of the United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9836317300796509,
            "question": "Is Edward Felten an American citizen?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8909444212913513,
            "question": "What is Edward Felten's citizenship?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8436594605445862,
            "question": "What is the citizenship status of Edward Felten?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6491986513137817,
            "question": "Edward Felten's nationality is?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5998879671096802,
            "question": "Where is Edward Felten from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5233514904975891,
            "question": "What nationality is Edward Felten?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4849903881549835,
            "question": "Where does Edward Felten reside?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46810635924339294,
            "question": "To which country does Edward Felten belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4211365878582001,
            "question": "In what country was Edward Felten born?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Edward Felten is a citizen of United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7678_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To which country does Edward Felten belong?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7678_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where does Edward Felten reside?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7678_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What nationality is Edward Felten?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7678_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7678_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7678_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7678_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7678_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7678_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7678_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7678_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7678_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7678_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7678_81.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports that Edward Felten is a citizen of the United States, as stated on his Wikipedia page (or DBpedia, judging by the file_path): \"Nationality: United States\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information provided in the documents supports that Edward Felten is a citizen of the United States. This can be inferred from his nationality being listed as \"United States\" and his involvement in U.S.-based initiatives and government roles, such as serving as Deputy U.S. Chief Technology Officer."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}